

INTERACTION DESIGNER

## **CONTACT**

Cra 17a #16-59 Jamundí, Colombia

(+57) 316 532 5256

jsebastianm1113@gmail.com

bit.ly/JMdesigner

### **FOLLOW ME**

Be behance.net/jsebastianfa54

in bit.ly/linkedinJohanM

# **LANGUAGE**

SPANISH: Native

ENGLISH: B2

### **TOOLS**

Figma Invision

Mendeley Adobe Suite

Github React

Sass Fierbase

Mongo DB Android

Wordpress Arduino

Slack Asana



# **ABOUT ME**

I am an interactive media design student who helps the planning, execution and development of digital products through design, guaranteeing high levels of innovation in the market.

I have developed my professional profile through UX Research, Interface Design (UI) and Front-End Development.



## **EDUCATION**

#### > INTERACTIVE MEDIA DESIGN

Aug 2015 - Nowadays

ICESI University, Santiago de Cali, Colombia



# **EXPERIENCE**

### > USER INTERFACE DESIGNER (WEB)

Aug 2019 - Jul 2020

### Angular Diseño más Interacción

Design and construction of user interface content. Development and execution of virtual prototypes for interactive web platforms at **Angular Diseño más Interacción - Digital Angency**.

#### > WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

#### **A Creative Work**

Development of user interfaces designs for Digital Agencies through agile tools like Wordpress at **A Creative Work - Web Offshoring**.

#### > ACADEMIC CONSULTANT - PROGRAMMING Sept

Sept 2018 - Jun 2019

#### **Icesi University**

Advice in the development with digital products with tools like Java, Javascript, CSS, HTML, Android, Arduino and React. Being consultant of all Interactive Media Design Students about algorithm programming and implementation strategies.

### > DESIGN MANAGER - GÜINEV

Jan 2018 - Jul 2020

### **Icesi University**

Manager and councilor of the design department of Interactive Media Design students group, contributing to the creation of illustrative strategies for the design profile of this major, at national and international level through events and transmedia concepts.



### **SKILLS**

UX DESIGN PROTOTYPE DESIGN

UI DESIGN HUMAN AND COMPUTER INTERACTION

UI DEVELOPMENT INFORMATION ARQUITECTURE

DESIGN RESEARCH EXPERIMENT DESIGN THROUGH STATISTICS